Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1910-1919
    - Harris, James Augustine, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Hartman, Roy Charles, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Hayden, Charles Ernest, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      Includes photographs; See also Faculty file
    - Hill, Charles Francis, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      1889-1939
    - Howe, Ivan Goodwin, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      1892-1960
    - James, Floyd Thomas, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Johnson, Howard Eckler, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      1882-1972?
    - Leonard, Milton Moot, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      1893-1984
    - Lyon, James Vernon, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      1891-1945
    - McCartny, Harry Charles, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      1885-1925
    - Mead, Lynn Howard, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      1890-1968
    - Moulthrop, Ralph Roy, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      1889-1972?
    - Murray, Benjamin Frank, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Oberle, Alfred, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      1882-1938
    - Price, Leo, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      1894-
    - Savage, Alfred, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      1889-1970
      From Montreal, Quebec, Canada
    - Schaefer, Fred Henry, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      1892-1963
    - Singleton, Garrett Archie, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Skinner, Charles Bailey, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Smith, Arthur Lewis, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Smith, Franklin DuBois, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Steele, Edward R., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 86)
      1890-1932
    - Sumner, William Henry, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 87)
      1892-1954
    - Tillson, Hobart Warren, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 88)
      1888-1970
    - Vann, George Herbert, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 89)
      1890-1946
    - Vara, Joseph J., 1914 (Box 3, Folder 90)
      1893-1970
    - Webber, Clarence Wentworth, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Wilson, Floyd Ephraim, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Winters, Raymond, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Wright, Lewis Horatio, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 94)
      1894-1974
    - Youmans, Ray Sedric, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 95)
      1892-1957
    - Zuber, Frank Pierce, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Allen, James Henry, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 97)
      1893-1990?
    - Baeszler, Alfred Thomas, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 98)
      1893-1954
    - Becker, Volney Minot, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 99)
      1892-
    - Bonnikson, Harry Peter, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Boshart, Charles Ralph, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 101)
      1892-1932
    - Brown, Albert Lyle, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 102)
      1892-1974?
    - Cornwell, Lloyd Rufus, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 103)
      1888-1931
    - Crosby, Joseph Fenton, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 104)
      1893-
    - Crowe, Lester Pierce, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Dassance, Leland Grant, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 106)
      1891-1925
    - Davis, Roscoe Erle, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 107)
      1891-1948
    - Franke, Adolph Otto, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 108)
      1872-1922
    - Halsey, Raymond Augustus, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      189?-1948
    - Hoyt, David Morris, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 110)
      1893-1955
    - Jansen, John Floyd, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Jones, Orrin Pritchard, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Krowl, John Charles, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 113)
      1890-1939
    - Mook, Herbert Richard, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 114)
      1893-1961
    - Moore, John Herbert, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Petersen, Peter Theodore, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 116)
      1888-1919
    - Regan, John Joseph, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 117)
      1892-1970
    - Regan, Stephen Paul, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 118)
      18??-1942
    - Schneidman, Samuel Albert, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 119)
      1894-1961
    - Shigley, James Fremont, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Sierk, Leo Carmi, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Smith, Reuben Elijah, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 122)
      1892-1972?
    - Spaulding, Roy Henry, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Trowbridge, William Wesley, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Vestal, Harold Clark, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 125)
      1894-1975
    - Webster, Carl Sperry, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 126)
      1893-1943
    - Webster, Louis Carlton, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Williams, Walter Wilkinson, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 128)
      1892-1988
      See also Collection #6547, Williams, Walter W. papers, 1916-1987
    - Altman, Irving Edward, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 129)
      1896-1972?
    - Ardell, Judson Warren, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 130)
      1982-1972?
    - Arnold, John Fletcher, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 131)
      1893-1927
    - Barringer, James Law, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 132)
      1892-1935
    - Bolenbaker, Roger Fraleigh, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 133)
      1894-1946
    - Caveney, Francis James, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 134)
      1889-1947
    - Clark, Frederick Conrad, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 135)
      1894-1949
    - Dalrymple, David Bennett Hill, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Dennington, Marion Edwin, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 137)
      1879-1945
    - Hewett, George Henry, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Hodges, Harry Gurdon, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 139)
      Various photographs
    - Hoyt, James Riccardo, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Klotz, Joseph Lee, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 141)
      1893-1976?
    - Latshaw, Joseph Bruce, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Long, William Michael, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 143)
      1893-1949
    - Meade, Bernard Clarence, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Moore, John Dudley, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 145)
      1890-1935
    - Quinn, Maurice Arthur, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 146)
      1892-1956
    - Ransley, George Nethaway, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Reed, Francis I., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Russell, Fay Franklin, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Rutan, Russell Conklyn, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 150)
      1896-1938
    - Schaefer,George Leonard, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Shindell, Samuel H., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 152)
      1893-1965
    - Shook, Louis Lathrop, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Skillman, George Sprague, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 154)
      1895-1917
    - Stotchik, Julius, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Sutterby, William Henry, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 156)
      1892-1968
    - Thomson, William Maxwell, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 157)
      1894-1968
    - Whitney, Ralph Steward, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 158)
      1893-1958
    - Arnett, Ross Harold, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Bard, George Philip, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Carpenter, Charles Milton, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 161)
      1895-1966
    - Claris, John Woodward, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 162)
      1893-1950
    - Conklin, Raymond LeRoy, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 163)
      1895-
    - Dederick, Frederick Van Dyke, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Derrick, George Webster, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Fanslau, Charles Edward, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 166)
      1896-
    - Gierke, Alfred Gustav, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 167)
      1894-1942
    - Gilman, Herbert Lester, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 168)
      1895-1982
    - Grace, Charles Oliver, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Graves, Joseph Napoleon, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Herzer, Philip Charles, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      1894-1960
    - Hopper, Earle Budd, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      1895-1967
    - Howe, Thomas Harold, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Kolar, Michael John, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Laird, Hugh David, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mabey, MacHenry, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Mallan, Daniel Henry, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Erwin Veranus, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      1893-1967
    - Moore, Lloyd Edward, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      1892-1990
    - Morris, Charles Van Wie, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Mould, Clarence William, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      1896-1939
    - Murrian, Leo Vincent, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      1895-1938
    - Neate, Nathan Menzo, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      1895-1948
    - Sager, Floyd Chauncey, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      1894-1986
    - Stack, John H., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      1886-1974?
    - Sturrock, Alexander Pollock, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      1891-1977?
    - Tucker, Talmage Thomas, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Waller, Ray Benson Potter, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      1893-1941
      Second African-American
    - Way, Walter Denslow, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      1895-1986
    - Weisman, Louis, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Woodruff, Frank Holmes, Jr., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Billings, William Arthur, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Blackberg, Nathan Solomon, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      1897-
    - Boardman, Don Arol, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      1895-1970
    - Brown, Charles Elmer, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Brunner, Leon Dispeau, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Brunson, Wright Abel, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      1894-1937
    - Connolly, Paul Tehan Ignatius, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Cooke, Gaylord Kell, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Cruickshanks, Fred, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      1890-1944
    - Finkelstein, Benjamin Jonathan, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Flannery, Joseph Michael, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      1892-1955
    - Fleming, Howard Fordham, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Frick, Edwin Jacob, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      1896-1941?
    - Fuller, Robert Wesley, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Gardner [Gershovsky], Hyman William, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      1891-1973?
    - Gilroy, Walter Emmet, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Gray, H. Paul, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      1896-1941
    - Greene, Harry Robert, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      1896-1963
    - Grinnells, Claude Delbert, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      1892-1976?
    - Hoyt, Floyd Erwin, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Hunt, George E., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      1895-1941?
    - Hust, Floyd Philip, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      1892-1927
    - Jackson, Abram John, Jr., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      1898-1975
    - Jenkins, DuBois, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Kelley, Francis Michael, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      See also Collection #6546, Kelley, Francis M. papers, 1910-1969
    - LaWare, Edward William, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1896-1974?
    - Leonard, Harsey King, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Lounsbery, Louis Martin, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Loveland, Benjamin Bristol, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      1897-1956
    - Markham, Miles Capron, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      1893-1976
    - Martin, Howard Eshelman, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      1894-1976?
    - McAuliff, John Leon, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - McCartney, Robert Ames, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Metzger, Herbert John, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Miller, Clarence Merton, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Myers, Harvey William, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Packer, Abraham, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Potter, Wilburn Herrick, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      1892-1967
    - Richardson, Solon Albert, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Scutt, Dana Rolland, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Seabrook, William Henry, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      1896-1950
    - Smith, Fenner C., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      1887-1929
    - Snow, Ralph, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Snyder, Walter C., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      1892-1924
    - Stafford, Ellis Carlton, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      1894-1969
    - Stone, Edward Stanley, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Tarr, Albert Jacob, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      1894-1976
    - Tripp, Lynn Howard, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Van Volkenberg, Horatio Luther, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      1898-1944
    - Waller, Owen Meredith, Jr., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      1895-1941
    - Whitmore, Mathew Franklin, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Wilkinson, Marshall Fisk, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 73)
      1895-1972?
    - Wynne, Harry P., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Zellner, Ansel Kenneth, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Benson, Joseph Phillips, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 76)
      1892-1948
    - Blau, Nathan F., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 77)
      1885-1972?
    - Chynoweth, Walter John, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Corwin, Louis Alfred, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Gorton, Raymond Vaughn, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      1893-1928
    - Houghton, Paul Roswell, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - LaGrange, DeWitt, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      1896-1951
      Includes 1920 NY State practice license
    - Muskovin, Albin, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Noonan, Henry Patrick, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      1895-1978
    - Parks, Wellington Edward, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Powell, Glenn John, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Scherago, Morris, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Townsend, Jay Griffith, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      189?-
    - Zepp, Clarence Peter, Sr., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 89)
      1892-1964
      Various photographs; AVMA president
  - 1920-1929
    - Brink, James Henry, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Camuti, Louis J., 1920 (Box 4, Folder 91)
      18??-1981
      No class photo; REPLACEMENT folder; content incomplete
    - Carpenter, Clifford Deane, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Conlin, William Jerome, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 93)
      1892-1952
    - Cushing, Edward Raymond, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - de Souza, Moacyr Alves, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Desson, Leonard Joseph, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Duncan, Charles Eugene, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 97)
      1895-1963
    - Fincher, Myron Gustin, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      1898-1981
      See also Faculty file and Collection #25-02-802, Fincher, Myron G. papers, 1908-1993
    - Friderici, Kenneth Schyler, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 99)
      1898-1974?
    - Helms, Orland Edward, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Johnston, Roy Campbell, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Laughlin, John, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Marsh, Herbert Edward, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 103)
      1888-1963
    - McBride, Earl James, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 104)
      1895-1926
    - McKinney, Robert Asa, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 105)
      1893-1960
    - Mills, Adrian Morse, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Montfort, Ellis Lindsey, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 107)
      1897-1975?
    - Pease, Donald Linus, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Robinson, Aubrey Eugene, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Russell, Alden Hesseltine, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Smith, Earl D., 1920 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Stephenson, Hadley Carruthers, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Sturrock, John, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Varley, James Richard, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - White, Floyd Henry, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Wilkinson, Raymond James, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 116)
      1896-1976
    - Bryant, Maynard Luther, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 117)
      1897-1941?
    - DeLaney, James Michael, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Dodge, Loren Newell, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Fuller, James Weast, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Glenn, Samuel, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 121)
      1894-1959
    - Grant, Wilbur F., 1921 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Hall, Walter Jay, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Harmon, Glenn Douglas, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 124)
      1898-
    - Herman, LeRoy Louis, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 125)
      1896-1969
    - McCoy, Charles Stickney, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 126)
      1899-1944
    - Morgan, Carlton James, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 127)
      1893-1975
    - O'Leary, Joseph Henry, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Paddock, Arthur James, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Rathbone, John Atkinson, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 130)
      1895-1962
    - Schwamm, George, Jr., 1921 (Box 4, Folder 131)
      1897-1934
    - Taylor, Donald Fay, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Bower, Laurence Robert, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 133)
      1899-1972?
    - Bullard, John Flower, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 134)
      1899-1976?
    - Caslick, Edward Albert, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 135)
      1896-1945
    - Cheney, David William, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - France, Morris Giles, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 137)
      1898-1977?
      Member of class of 1921, but received DVM in 1922
    - LaFrance, John, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 138)
      1900-1962
    - Loope, Clarence Leroy, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - McBride, Frank, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 140)
      1897-1973
    - Monroe, Roswell Miller, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 141)
      1899-
    - Montemayor, Mariano Rangel, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Roberts, Clarence Roger, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 143)
      1900-
    - Ruehle, Otto, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Turner, John Corydon [or Condon], 1922 (Box 4, Folder 145)
      1899-1975
    - Bogan, James Joseph, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 146)
      1901-1948
    - Bogan, John Lawrence, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 147)
      1900-1942
    - Bramer, Clarence Newell, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 148)
      1901-
    - Brenning, Irwin Frederick, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Brown, Ellsworth Sheffer, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 150)
      1896-1948
    - Brunett, Earl Louis, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 151)
      1898-1943
    - Cain, Charles B., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 152)
      1900-1943
    - Conlon, Lawrence Hayes, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 153)
      1902-1986
    - DeVolt, Harold Moon, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Dohm, William Herman, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Donahoe, Walter Richard, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 156)
      1902-1934
    - Freer, Charles Bessely, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Freer, George Hoyt, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 158)
      1895-1976
    - Hall, Frederick Abbey, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Harden, James Henry Joseph, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 160)
      1897-1953
    - Maus, Frank Charles, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 161)
      1898-1939
    - Merritt, Clifford Alexander, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 162)
      1902-1960
    - Moersfelder, William John, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Robens, William Glenn, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Sherwood, James Elias, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Sholl, Lloyd Banks, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      1894-1958
    - Smith, Philip Rudolph Botha, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Sutton, Harry William, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      1897-1952
    - Tremlett, James Richard, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      1898-1958
    - Vaselius, George Gustav Emil, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      1884-1933
    - Whipple, Earl Franklin, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      1899-1957
    - Wooden, Aubrey Arthur, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      1896-1962?
    - Canary, Maurice DeGraff, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      1902-1971
    - Cheney, John Baird, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      1902-1994
    - Cox, Herbert Morris, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Crawford, William Rush, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      1893-1942
    - DeCamp, Clayton Earl, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      1897-1971
    - Foote, Howard John, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      1900-1975?
    - Kern, Clyde Lewis, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      1897-1967
    - Ludins, George Horace, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      1902-19??
    - Marshall, James Sumner, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      1899-1951
      Includes NYC practice certificate
    - McMurray, Harold Benjamin, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      1894-1957
    - Miller, Robert Mathias, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Miller, Trelford Simpson, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      1899-1948
    - Mires, Maynard Harold, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      1894-1991
    - Nelson, Harold George, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      1899-1946
    - Nevens, Milton Alson, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Nevitt, John Victor, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Stringham, George Lauder, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Taylor, Theodore Fred, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Whiting, Ralph Earl, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      1898-1927
    - Bassett, Dell Clare, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      1899-1945
    - Gibbons, Richard Vincent, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Gibbons, Walter Joseph, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      1903-1977
    - Gordon, Reuben, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Nugent, William Kemp, Jr., 1925 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      1902-
    - Raymond, Paul Albert, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Rife, Charles Cornelius, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      1901-1982
    - Yashkin, Adalyn Flora Schoenfeld, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      1903-1950
      Second woman graduate
    - Volgenau, Robert Herman, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      1904-
    - Bacon, John, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      1904-1954
    - Bardwell, Robert Hine, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      1900-1944
    - Bolton, Clarence Edward, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      1903-1974?
    - Crawford, John Elliott, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      1903-
    - Davidson, Arthur Colwell, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      1901-1973
    - DeMott, Andre Ray, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Dennis, William Albert, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Engle, Joseph Branin, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      1903-1991
    - Ghazarian, Vrouir, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      19??-1988
      From Armenia
    - Goodman, Laurence William, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      1902-1972?
    - Kennelly, Edward Martin, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Miller, Walter Rohrer, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      1902-2001
    - Morris, Mark Loren, Sr., 1926 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      1900-1993
    - Olafson, Peter, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      1897-1985
      See also Faculty file and Collection #24-2-2234, Olafson, Peter papers, [ca. 1920-1984]
    - Peterson, John Jacob, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Reed, Francis Irving, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Tabor, Stevens Giddings, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      1903-1978
    - ter Kuile, Roger Couvelle, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      1903-1994
    - Wilder, Horace Frederick, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1903-1968
    - Zeissig, Alexander, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      1901-1974
      See also Collection #6642, Zeissig, Alexander, papers, 1959-1966
    - Andrews, Donald Holston, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      1902-1946
    - Aronson, Harry Preston, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      1904-1962
    - Asmus, Reimer August, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1903-1972?
    - Bennehoff, James De Sett, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Booth, Russell Berkins, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Caslick, William, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      1901-1956
    - Crawford, James Stuart, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      1905-
    - Ferguson, Stanley Eugene, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      1905-1962
    - Ford, Dana Delancey, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Globus, Robert, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Grace, Reginald Linus, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      1906-
      See also Collection #37-5-3694m, Grace, Reginald L., miscellany, 1923-1927
    - Hilbert, Arnold Edward, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      1902-1975
    - Hoag, Warren Fowler, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Jaynes, Cornelia, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      1895-1969
      Third woman graduate
    - Keyes, Kenneth Wilbur, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Lockwood, Willard G., 1927 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      1882-1951
    - Newman, Alphonso Collins, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - O'Neil, Robert Kenneth, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      1904-1968
    - Parker, Harold Croft, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Rindell, Arthur Mathias, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Sellman, William Joseph, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Stone, Garland Douglass, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Thomson, John Caephus, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      1904-1979
    - Tice, Floyd Joseph, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Trayford, Arthur, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Wright, Stuart Leroy, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      1898-1967
    - Goubeaud, Charles Joseph, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      1903-1960
    - Greenway, John Ernest, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      1906-1964
    - Hilbert, Kenneth Franklin, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Hopson, George Henry, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 88)
      1903-1967
    - Kelly, Wayne Arthur, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 89)
      1905-1954
    - Lee, Myrle Faber, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - MacKellar, Robert Stuart, Jr., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - McIntosh, John Pierce, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Messer, Lykergus William, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 93)
      1900-1974?
    - Nichols, Rudolph Edward, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Noonan, Cyril James, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Parshall, Charles Jonas, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      1902-1977
    - Poley, Philip, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      1904-1948
    - Thomas, William A., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Ulmer, William Ernest, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 99)